Guide to the Records of Director of Academic Program Review, Barnett Hamberger 1972-2003 RG 9.7 RG 9.7
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Community Service Council, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - CT, undated (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Conference Center, undated (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Credit Practices, undated (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Disc Academic Programs, undated (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Einstein Chair, undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058582 3
  - Fac & Staff Assistance Program Policy Statement, undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Salary Survey, undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Finances, undated (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - American Council on Ed Dir of Gov't Relations, undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Grad Comm., 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Grad Comm., 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Grad Rates, undated (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Heights Sale, undated (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - International Dimension Reports, undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Memoranda to L. Jay Oliva, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Memoranda to L. Jay Oliva, 1991-1993 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Mission Statements, undated (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - National Study of Post-Secondary Faculty, 1992-1994 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - NJ Inst of Higher Ed, undated (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Policies Concerning Courses and Programs Offered Off-Campus, undated (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - NYU--Polytechnic Institute of New York, undated (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Program Terminations, undated (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Majors Registration, 1992-1994 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Registration, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Responses to SED Concerning Other Inst, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Response to SED, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - CCNY Review, undated (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - SED, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - SED Proposed Regulations on Financial Assistance, undated (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - SED Financial Regulations, 1990-1994 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - State Master Plan Report, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - State Master Plan Report, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Athletics, 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Athletics, 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Athletics--Coke, 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Athletics, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058569 0
  - Athletics, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Athletics--Academics, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Athletics--Academics, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Basketball Attendance, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Basketball Attendance, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Basketball Away Receptions, 1990-1994 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Basketball Tournaments, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Athletics--Coke, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Athletics Endowment Fund, 1992-1994 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Athletics Endowment, 1991-1992 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Graduation Rates, undated (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Athletic History, undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Athletic Honor Roll, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Athletic Honor Roll, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Athletic Graduation Report, 1991-1993 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - State Master Plan--Issue Reports, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Student Activities, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Students' Right to Know, undated (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Summer of Service, undated (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Surveys, undated (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Tuition Assistance Program Audit Rep., undated (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - U of Navarra (Spain), undated (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Bureau of Veterans Education, undated (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Westchester County Report, undated (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Athletic News+H1472, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058578 1
  - Athletic News, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Athletics -- New Teams, 1991-1994 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Press Releases, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Press Releases, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Press Releases, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Athletics -- Peterson's Letter, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Athletics -- Peterson's Letter, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Schedules, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Transcripts [RESTRICTED], 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Tutors, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Varsity Club, undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Varsity Club/Athletic Field Fund Drive, undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - VBC Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Athletics -- Violet Line, undated (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Coles Center, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Coles, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Coles Administration, undated (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Coles/Academic Affairs -- Computer, undated (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Coles All-University Meets, undated (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Coles Alumni Memberships, 1990-1994 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Coles Capital Reserve, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Coles Capital Reserve, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Coles Clubs, undated (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Coles Center Complaints, undated (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Coles Community Memberships, 1990-1994 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Coles Development Campaign, 1988-1994 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Coles Emergency Procedures, undated (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Coles Employee-of-the-Month, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Coles Endowment Fund, 1989-1994 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Coles Golf/Tennis Outing, undated (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Coles Golf Tournament, undated (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Coles Graduate Assistant, undated (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Coles Hockey Rink, undated (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Coles Center ID Access, undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058581 5
  - Coles Job Descriptions, undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Coles Licensing, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Coles Licensing, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Coles Pro-Shop, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Coles Pro-Shop, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Coles Recreation, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Coles Registration, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Coles Registration, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Resumes [RESTRICTED MATERIAL], undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Advisory Board Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Achievement Awards, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Advisory Board, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Achievement Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Coles SCE, undated (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Coles Summer Memberships, 1990-1994 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Coles Telephone Usage (Codes 214 & 216), undated (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Coles Usage, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - NCAA, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - NCAA, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - NCAA, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - NCAA, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - NCAA Audit, undated (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Athletics -- National Collegiate Athletic Association Gender-Equity Study, 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - NCAA Enrollment -- Peterson's Report, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - NCAA Enrollment -- Peterson's Report, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - NCAA -- President's Commission, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - NCAA Rules, undated (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - NCAA Self-Study, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - NCAA Self-Study, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - UAA, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058584 9
  - UAA, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - UAA Delegates Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - UAA Executive Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - UAA Presidents Council, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - UAA Presidents Council, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - UAA Schedules, 1990-1994 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - FERPA Clearinghouse, undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - FERPA Requests, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - FERPA Requests, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - FERPA Requests, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - FERPA Information, undated (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - FERPA Guidelines, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - FERPA Guidelines, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - FERPA Materials, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Athletics, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058591 4
  - Athletics, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Athletics Academic Honor Roll, 1994-1996 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Achievement Awards, 1994-1996 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Advisory Board, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Basketball, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Athletics- Gymnastics, undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058590 6
  - Athletics- Ice Hockey, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Athletics Personnel, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Athletics- Torch Escort, undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Athletics- Summer Camps, undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Athletics- Varsity Club, undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Athletics- Varsity Club, undated (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Athletics- Varsity Club, undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Athletics- Varsity Club, undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Athletics- Violet Booster Club, undated (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Athletics- Violet Booster Club, undated (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Community Service Council, undated (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Community Service Council, undated (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Community Service Council, undated (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - NCAA, 1994-1995 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058589 8
  - NCAA, 1994-1995 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - NCAA, 1994-1995 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - NCAA, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - NCAA, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - UAA, 1994-1995 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - UAA, 1994-1995 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - UAA, 1994-1995 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - UAA, 1994-1995 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - UAA, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - UAA, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - UAA, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - UAA, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - UAA, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - UAA--10th Anniversary Video, undated (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - UAA--10th Anniversary Video, undated (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - General Athletic Field, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058599 7
  - General Athletic Field, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - General Athletic Field, 1995-1996 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - General Athletic Field, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - General Athletic Field, undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Field Architects, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Field- Randall's Island, 1991-1993 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Fields- Battery Park City, undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Fields- Brooklyn Sports Foundation, undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - NJ Athletic Field, 1992-1993 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Athletics Field Construction, undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Field Costs, undated (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Field Dimensions, undated (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Field- East River Park, undated (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Athletic Field- NJDEP Environment, undated (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Athletic Field- Equipment, undated (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - NJ Athletic Field, 1991-1992 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - NJ Athletic Field Fundraising, 1991-1992 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Athletic Field Fundraising, 1992-1993 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Athletic Field Fundraising, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Athletic Field Fundraising, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Athletic Fields- Gateway Nat'l Park, undated (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Athletic Fields- Olympics, undated (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Athletic Fields- Governor's Island, undated (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Athletic Field HRPC, undated (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Athletic Field- Weehawken History, undated (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Athletic Field- Meeting Minutes, undated (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Athletic Field- NJDEP, undated (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Athletic Field/NJ Department of Environmental Protections, 1992-1993 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - NJ Athletic Field Plans, 1992-1993 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - NJ Athletic Field Plans, 1992-1993 (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - NJ Athletic Field Plans, 1991-1992 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Athletic Fields- NYC Parks, undated (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Athletic Field Surfaces, undated (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Athletic Restricted Funds, 1992-1994 (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - Athletic Field Waterfront Development Applications, undated (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - NJ Athletic Field Weehawken School System, 1992-1994 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058598 9
  - Athletic Field Roosevelt Island, 1990-1991 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Field NJ Weehawken, undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Field- Weehawken Community Use, undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Field- Weehawken Schools, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Field- Weehawken Plans, undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Field- Weehawken Clubhouse, undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Coles, 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Policy Handbook for Intercollegiate Athletics/Coles Program Guide, undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Coles, 1996-1997 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Coles, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Coles Alumni Memberships, undated (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Coles Bobcat Buddies, undated (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Coles Café, undated (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Coles Clubs, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Coles Memberships, 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Coles Memberships, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Coles Employee of Month, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Coles Guest Passes, undated (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Coles Licensing, 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Coles Licensing, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Coles Community Memberships, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Coles Maintenance and Matriculation, undated (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Coles Pro Shop, 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Coles Pro Shop, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Coles Recreation, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Coles Roof, Coles Roof-Top Playground, 1985-1987 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Coles Trustees Memberships, undated (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Coles Trustees Memberships, 1990-1994 (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Coles Usage, 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Coles Usage, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - Coles Homepage/Webpage, undated (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - Coles Advisory, 1996-1997 (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - Athletic Chelsea Piers- Bus Service, undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058597 1
  - Athletic Chelsea Piers, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Chelsea Piers, undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Enrollment Report, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Presidents Commission, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Presidents Commission, undated (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Presidents Commission, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - NCAA Presidents Commission, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - NCAA Presidents Council, 1995-1996 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - NCAA Self Study, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - UAA Ad Hoc Committee on Grads & Profs, undated (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - UAA Delegates Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Homepage, undated (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - UAA Presidents Council, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - SEHNAP/ Weehawken Schools, 1992-1994 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058585 6
  - CAS Washington Semester, undated (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - University Development, undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Enrollment Reports, 1988-1994 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Resource Network, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Resource Network, undated (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Government Relations, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Government Relations, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Graduation Rates, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Memoranda to LJO, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Manhattanville, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Middle States, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - MSA, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Middle States Assocation, 1993-1994 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Middle States Assocation, 1992-1993 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - MSA Study Abroad, 1988-1994 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - MSA Eval/NYU in Spain, 1992-1994 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - NYU in Spain, undated (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Questionnaires (2), undated (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Registration, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Registration, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Responses to SED, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Responses to SED, undated (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Responses to SED concerning other institutions, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Student Activities, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Student Information System, undated (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - SIS/Ferpa Security Committee, undated (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - SIS Security Video, undated (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - SIS Security Committee (2), undated (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - State Postsecondary Review Program, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058587 2
  - State Postsecondary Review Program, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Trustees, undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Athletics/Coles- Budget Reduction, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Athletic/Coles Salaries, 1996-1997 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Ath/Coles Salary Worksheets, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Ath/Coles Salary Worksheets, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Ath/Coles Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Athletics Budgets, 1996-1997 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Athletics Budgets, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Athletics Budgets, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Field Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Income, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Income, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Athletic Restricted, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Athletic Restricted, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Fencing Budgets, undated (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Athletic Field- Staff and Team Costs, undated (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Athletics--Coles Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Coles Salary Worksheets, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Ath Coles Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Coles Budgets, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Coles Budgets, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Coles Budgets, 1996-1997 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Coles Budgets, 1997-1998 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Coles Capital Reserve, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Coles Capital Reserve, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Coles Plant Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Coles Plant Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Athletics- Chelsea Piers Agreement, undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058600 3
  - Chelsea Piers Agreement Background, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Chelsea Piers Contract- Background, undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Chelsea Piers Contract- Drafts, undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Chelsea Piers Final Agreement, undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Athletic- Coca Cola, 1998-1999 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Athletic- Coca Cola, 1997-1998 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Athletic- Coca Cola, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Athletic- Coca Cola, 1995-1996 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Athletic- Coca Cola, 1994-1995 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - CAS Program Terminations, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - CAS, 1995-1996 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - CAS, 1994-1995 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - CAS, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - CAS, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Dentistry, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Dentistry Accreditation, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Dentistry, 1995-1996 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Dentistry, 1994-1995 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Dentistry, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Dentistry, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Dentistry, 1991-1992 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Dentistry, 1988-1991 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Dentistry- Puerto Rico, undated (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Dentistry- SED/NERB, undated (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Education, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Education Accreditation, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Education DA, 1995-1997 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Education, 1995-1996 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - School of Ed Accreditation, 1995-1996 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - School of Ed Accreditation, 1994-1995 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - School of Ed Program Terminations, 1994-1997 (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - Education Accreditation, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 33)
  - School of Ed, 1992-1994 (Box 77, Folder 34)
  - SEHNAP, 1992-1994 (Box 77, Folder 35)
  - SEHNAP, 1991-1992 (Box 77, Folder 36)
  - SEHNAP, 1988-1989 (Box 77, Folder 37)
  - FAS, 1995-1996 (Box 77, Folder 38)
  - FAS Hebrew and Judaic Studies, undated (Box 77, Folder 39)
  - Gallatin, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 40)
  - Gallatin, 1995-1996 (Box 77, Folder 41)
  - GSAS, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058586 4
  - GSAS, 1995-1996 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - GSAS, 1994-1995 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - GSAS, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - GSAS, 1992-1993 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - GSAS Humanities, undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - GSAS Ph.D. Neural Science Program (3), undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - GSAS- Slavic Ph.D, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Library Program, undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Law, 1995-1996 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Law School, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Law School, 1989-1992 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Medicine--New Programs, 1994-1996 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - SCE, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - SCE Accreditation, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - SCE, 1995-1996 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - SCE (2), 1994-1995 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - SCE, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - SCE (2), 1992-1993 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - SCE Termination, undated (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - SCE Honors, undated (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - SSW, 1995-1996 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - SSW, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - SSW, 1992-1993 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Stern School of Business Grad, 1995-1996 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Stern-Grad, 1995-1996 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Stern-Grad, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Stern School of Business, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Stern UG, 1992-1993 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - SSB, 1987-1993 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - TSOA, 1995-1996 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - TSOA, 1992-1994 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Wagner School, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Wagner, 1995-1996 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Wagner School of Business, 1992-1994 (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Wagner School of Business, 1990-1992 (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - MS Reports/Letters, undated (Box 79, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058594 8
  - Middle States Assocation, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Background Info, undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - MSA Executive Summary, undated (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - MSA Rice Committee, undated (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Tean, undated (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Heeger Committee, undated (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Marcess Committee, undated (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - MSA Self Study (2), 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Middle States 1994 Report Vol. 1 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Middle States 1994 Report Vol. II (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Middle States 1994 Report Vol. III (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Middle States Report Epilogue, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Middle States Report Apprendices, and other attachments, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - MSA Report Vol II Education and Research, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - MSA Self Study: Deans Briefing, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - MSA Self Study: Organization, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - MSA Self-Study: Evaluation Outline, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - MSA Int'l Educ & Research Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Middle States Study Abroad, 1995-1996 (Box 79, Folder 20)